Hu-hu-hu!
Young master Yuuran, breakfast is the
first source of each day’s energy.
You musn’t go without it!
Okay.
I’ll get revenge for Big bro Yuuro!
Uooooooooh!
Hu-Hu-Hu!!
That doesn’t look like Rush Duel training…
If Yuujin-nii-san loses, the opponent's
side will have two points.
When that happens…
There’s no way Yuujin-nii-san will lose, Yuuou.
I only want him to duel with the
resolve to quit being president if he loses.
Not yet, not yet!
That’s all I wanted to say, Yuuka-nee-san.
Gh…!
UOOOOOOOOOOOOOOH!!
What?!
HAAAAAAAAAAH!!!!
The taste of salt...
So this is a sea from Earth, huh.
Hm?
Go enjoy, feel, believe, and plunge into the light!
For some reason, when I looked up at the sun, I sneezed
A weird action, satisfaction, a hunch that something would happen
On those stifling days, come here when you're tired
Keep chasing your impulsive urges, for the ordinary is boring
To your turn that belongs to no one else
To the road's end that nobody sees
To our Harevutai that's like no one else's
greatest stage
I wanna enjoy, feel, believe, and kick the earth!
Limit break past your dreams and aim for that meteor!
We'll go beyond that boundary and surpass it!
Believe in that light shining in your hands!
Go enjoy, feel, believe, and plunge into the light!
Rush! Rush! Rush! Rush Duel!
Let's go Rush! Let's go Rush!
subbed by entameSubs
find all releases @ entamesubs.tumblr.com
The president who loves the sea, Goha Yuujin!!
The next opponent is "some guy riding a dolphin"?!
Yuujin and the Sea
The Rush Duel Robot has been
moving this whole time, huh…
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6...
7, 7!
7, 7, 7!
Taking Rush Duels hostage
like that... It's unforgivable!
The program seems to
already be under a burden…
The Six Goha Siblings... they
cannot be underestimated.
But y’know!
From now on, all we need to
do is win six times, right?
That’s the spirit!
Besides, Yuuga becoming a Goha
employee is just unthinkable.
Huh?
umi o umi
O sea, my sea!
ore no koibito
My previous lover.
Blue and wide and filled with salt~
aoku hiroi ore no shiomizu
LOVE YOU! LOVE YOOU!
MY SEAAA!
Aha~
Uh…
That’s…
A boat…?
Can you even call that a boat?
IT’S A BOAT!
Heh! I’m the second brother of the
six Goha President Siblings!
Thriving muscles!
Macho and looking good!
A man of the sea!
So the second one is him...
Hu-hu-hu!
A man of the sea…?
When did he become like that?
Is this a phase?
I’m counting on you, Saionji Neil!
Mr. President's exclusive duel stage: unleash.
Wh-What's happening now?!
Waaaah!
You’re amazing, Neil!
Is this…
The sea?!
Yay, it’s the sea!
Go! Yuuro!
Romin-kun!
Are you okay?
Th-Thanks…
My break just now was perfect, wasn't it?
If I had been 0.1 seconds faster or
slower, I would have failed to catch you.
Yuuro, why are you here?
I became a student here.
Goha 7th Elementary is now my race track.
HUH?!
Yuuro-nii-san…!
To think that you’d have to attend
the same school as them…!
It’s the sea...
Swirl…!
Ah, it has now become very sea-like.
Alright, next is…
Here, go change.
Get changed now!
Ta-daaa!
Wow, this is cute!
Romin-chan!!
Urk!
ROMIN PUNCH!
Romin—!
KICK!
Geez, I can’t let my guard down for a second.
It seems like you’re finally ready.
Well then, let’s begin!
Alright, come at me, Oudou Yuuga!
Wh-What?
I can’t swim though…
Don’t worry, Yuuga.
I’ll duel today!
Ah, thanks!
I’m counting on you, Luke!
Heh! The King of Duels is your opponent!
"The King of Duels", you say?
Well, whatever.
Let’s go!
As the sea breeze blows, I do as I please!
RUSH DUEL!
The man of the sea’s turn! Draw!
Assemble, Sea Serpents!
I summon Takriminos and Light Dolphin!
Light Dolphin is so cute!
I activate the field spell, Umi!
The ATK and DEF of Sea Serpent-types
on both of our fields go up by 200!
I activate Light Dolphin’s effect! I draw one!
I sacrifice both Takriminos and Light Dolphin to tribute summon Spike Seadra and Dolphin King Iruqua!
He’s just a dolphin, but he’s a king?!
As per Umi’s effect, they both gain 200 ATK!
Not bad, you Sea Serpents.
I haven’t seen many of
these cards before, Yuujin.
Huh?
Big brother!
I’ve obtained the treasure of the sea
and become a man of the sea!
Hm?
It all started when I met him...
Iruman.
< You, man of the sea. >
< Would you take this treasure? >
Treasure, you say?
I will accept it gladly.
And that’s what happened.
You can speak dolphin?
I mean, I can speak pigeon.
Coo-Luke-coo!
Ugh.
I set a card!
Then the man of the sea ends his turn!
My turn, draw!
I summon Dragolite, The
Fire Dragon, and Sylphydra!
I sacrifice two!
Tribute summon!
Right now,
within my universe,
the seven supernovas
gamma-ray burst!
Even if you tell me to stop, it's too late!
Even if you tell me to stop, it's too late!!
There's a reason I said it twice.
Come out, Dragias the Striking Dragon!
I send the top card of my deck to the
grave to activate Dragias' effect!
Gias Charge!
I set a card.
Go, Dragias!
Striking Light Bullet of Explosive Supremacy!
I'm still in the fight!
Dragon King Strike of Annihilative Supremacy!
He's destroyed all of Yuujin's monsters!
Hm.
Sylphydra direct attacks!
Since you declared a direct attack, I can now...
Activate Iruqua's Raging Waves!
All face-up attack monsters on your
field are switched to defense!
Wh-What?!
And then I can special summon
Dolphin King Iruqua from my grave!
Thanks to Umi's effect, Dolphin King
Iruqua's ATK goes up by 200!
Ugh... I end my turn.
Heh.
Man of the sea's turn, draw!
I activate Grand Extreme!
Ah, this happiness...
I'm happiest when I'm with Sea Serpent-types.
Hah?
Until the duel's over, I...
Won't ever let you go.
Come!
Levia-Dragon - Daedalus!
Grand Extreme's effect returns The Fire Dragon, Dragolite, and Bunker Strike from your GY to your deck.
And then with Umi's effect, Daedalus'
ATK goes up from 2600 to 2800!
It’s too early to be speechless!
I send Umi to the graveyard!
And activate Daedalus's effect!
Destruction Sea Burial!
All cards on both our fields
besides Daedalus are destroyed!
What?!
Ah!
All of them get destroyed?!
It has an effect that powerful?!
Luke’s monsters are all gone...
Daedalus's ATK goes back
down from 2800 to 2600.
And!
There's more?!
I discard a card to activate Shape of Aqua!
I special summon the WATER attribute
Dolphin King Iruqua from my graveyard!
Though its ATK goes down by 800.
Since he had Shape of Aqua, he could
destroy his own cards without restraint.
All of his cards have incredible effects...
Maybe Yuujin really did
obtain the treasure of the seas.
I set a card!
Dolphin King Iruka direct attacks!
Levia Stream!
How strong!
The man of the sea's turn end.
My turn, draw!
I summon Tenacity Dragon,
Palm-Sized Drago, and Triad Drago!
Triad Dragon's effect activates!
I draw one!
I sacrifice Palm-Sized Drago and
Triad Drago to tribute summon!
A fist meta-hardened by hidden feelings!
Pack yourself meta-full with fighting spirit and you'll see!
Blow away the meter inside your heart, and beyond this galaxy's long wormhole...
You'll find the Andro-meta Galaxy!
Give 'em a meta-meta beating!
Metagias the Steelstriking Dragon!
He managed to summon a level 7 monster, but...
It can't beat Daedalus.
I send Nightbringer to the grave
to activate Metagias' effect!
Until the end of this turn, this card
cannot be destroyed by trap effects.
Then I summon Tenacity Dragon!
I send the top card of my deck
to the grave to activate its effect!
Daedalus's ATK goes down by 400!
Now its ATK is lower than Metagias!
Ngh!
And then, I can set Dragon's
Tenacity from my graveyard.
I have another Tenacity Dragon, you know!
Huh?
That means I get to activate
the same effect again!
What?!
Luke-kun, nice tenacity!
Tenacity Dragon's effect activates!
Daedalus's ATK goes down by another 400!
Let's go, Metagias!
Attack it!
And now!
I activate Dolphin Counter!
When my opponent declares an attack, Dolphin Counter activates by returning Umi to my deck!
And!
It destroys the monster on your
field with the highest ATK!
Ah!
How naive!
Metagias cannot be destroyed by trap effects!
Dolphin Counter also lets me draw one!
And if that drawn card is Umi, then...
Then?
If it's Umi, then...
Then?!
You'll take 500 damage!
What?!
Luke only has—
—200 LP, so if he takes this—
—he'll lose!
O seas!
Lend me your power!
Now come, Umi!
Umi!
Creek?!
Huh? The sea's—?!
Ah!
Kaizo?
Hm?
Wait, this is—!
Don't tell me...
He unplugged the ocean.
The sea~ the sea~
Ah!
Oh...
Th-The sea!
My sea has...!
Metagias!
Iron-Star Bullet of Explosive Supremacy!
Now for Iruqua!
Steel King Strike of Annihilative Supremacy!
Both of you go now!
Direct attack!
O seeeaaaa!!
Yuujin...
Victor: Luke
Of course, of course.
Good job, Luke-kun!
What a huge comeback!
Now we're up 2 points!
This is just as expected for the King of Duels.
You've come.
I take responsibility for this loss and hereby declare my resignation as a president of Goha.
I guess I still have some training to do.
O sea!
Yuujin's resignation has been acknowledged.
Who will fight next?
Don't tell me it's young master Yuuran...
Looks like it's my turn to bat.
Honestly, what even are the
"6 Goha President Siblings"?
You guys were all just playing carefree out in space on your starship until a little while ago!
Kojima Yoshio’s Rush Duel Fun Time!
Phys-Ed!
Hey, everyone! Wanna duel today, too?
I’m Kojima Yoshio!
Now, I’m gonna announce today’s theme!
Let’s Practice a Cool Draw!
It’s my turn! Draw!
Ahhhh, that’s so cool!
Well, let Yoshio try it too!
My turn!
Draw!
Ah, wait, it’s the other way around!
The back that's supposed to be far beyond
Oops.
Divine Draw!
is out of sight
Draw!
Roa-sama! <3
There's no map leading to the goal
I just. Y’know, I had to go “Roa-sama” once!
So which way should I even go?
Well, why don’t I try it?
I had planned on standing alone
Divine
Draw!
But now, you're by my side
So? Was I very Roa?
But y’know, I wanna make my own original draw.
and that isn't bad at all
Even if my hands can't reach
the future I want to grasp
Well, why don’t I try it?
Alright! Here I go!
and the dreams I want to come true
still remain as dreams
That’s unrelated! Draw!
Let's sing as loud as we can!
Oh-Pa-Pi!
As long as I walk beside you
That’s unrelated! Draw!
Tomorrow will surely surpass today!
Oh-Pa-Pi!
Well, how was it? How was it?
I will surely surpass the me of today!
Ah, it was funny, right?
I can hear you laughing! Thank you!
All of you should try making an original draw too!
See you next time! Bye bye!
translations/subbing: entame
proofreading: angelthinktank
timing help: eljin
The birth of Goha City's new pro baseball team!!
Members of Goha 7th are also gonna take the test to join!!